

CONTACT DETAILS

- +57 316 536 7542
- sebasisaza_27@hotmail.com
- Street 9 12 48, Santa Rosa de Cabal, Colombia
- https://github.com/sebasisaza
- in <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/sebastian-isaza/</u>

SKILLS

- •••• Angular
- •••• Node.js
- •••• Vue.js
- ••• .NET
- ••• SQL Server
- •••• Mongo DB

LANGUAJES

- •••• English
- •••• Spanish

SEBASTIAN ISAZA C.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Developer with 7+ years building and executing web applications in different fields. Highly experienced in all stages of advanced web development. Knowledge in user interface, testing and debugging processes. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, accomplish the set goals, as well as collaborate as part of a team.

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Nearsure | November 2021 - Current

Making a reskin of a medical control software, using Anuglar, also migrating services to Node.js, according to the customer needs. Adding new features and solving some bugs through the development process in addition to joining scrum ceremonies.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

XpertGroup SAS | March 2021 - September 2021

Analyze project requirements, translating specifications into functional application components.

BACKEND DEVELOPER

ControlT | April 2019 - March 2021

Support and improvement to a web application needed for cargo transport and vehicle routes control web application.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Cinnco | November 2016 - October 2018

Planning and execution of web applications according to the needs of each client.

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

Indra | December 2015 - June 2016

Planning and execution of web applications according to the needs of each client.

EDUCATION

SYSTEMS ENGINEERING AND COMPUTING DEGREE

Technological University of Pereira